好了 我们再玩一次 好吗？
All right, let's play one more time, okay?
记得 如果我赢了 你不可以搬去巴黎
And remember, if I win, you do not move to Paris.
好吧 没想到我居然会冒这种险 不过 来吧
Okay. I can't believe I'm risking this again, but you're on.
好的 乔伊 记得规矩吧 正面算我赢 背面算你输
All right, Joe, you remember the rules. Heads, I win. Tails, you lose.
丢就是了
Just flip.
- 背面   - 可恶
- Tails!    - Damn it!
我们想在七点左右 帮你办个送别派对
So we thought we'd throw you a little going-away party around 7.
好啊
Oh, that sounds good.
瑞秋 你明天要走 不用才丁包吗？
Hey, Rach, you're leaving tomorrow. Shouldn't you be packing?
- 都好了   - 不可能吧
- It's all done.    - Oh, yeah, right.
好像我今天早上洗完澡之后 就随便把毛巾丢在地上一样
And after I took a shower this morning, I just threw my towel on the floor.
- 天啊 连开玩笑都让人难过   - 对啊
- Oh, God, it hurts to even joke about it.    - I know.
亲爱的 真的 我都收好了 我要带的行李都放在房间里了
Honey, seriously, I did it all. The luggage that I'm taking is in the bedroom.
这是艾玛要带到巴黎的东西 这些是我要寄去的
This is Emma's Paris stuff. These are the boxes that I'm having shipped...
那是我要在飞机上吃的三明治
...and that's the sandwich I made for the plane.
- 好吧 还算不错啦   - 当然
- Okay, you've done some good work.    - Yeah.
那你的随身行李呢？
What about your carry-ons?
所有我需要的东西 都在这里
Oh, well, everything that I need is in here...
我的旅游证件就在台面上
...and my travel documents are on the counter...
依照我需要的顺序排好了
...organized in the order that I will be needing them.
天啊 我没东西可以教你了
Oh, my God. I have nothing left to teach you.
- 你的护照在哪里？ - 应该在机票旁边
- Where's your passport?    - It should be next to my plane ticket.
- 并没有   - 怎么会呢？还是我放在这里？
- Well, it's not.    - What? Maybe I put it in here?
也没有在这里
Oh! Oh, it's not in there!
不 我一定是把它一起装箱了
Oh, no, I must have packed it in one of these boxes!
- 没关系 我来帮你找   - 可恶
- Here, let me help you.     - Shoot.
不敢相信我会这样
I can't believe I did this.
我现在说拿了她的护照 还会好笑吗？
At what point did it stop being funny that I took her passport?
真不相信 再三个星期就要生了
Oh, wow, can you believe you're only three weeks away?
对啊
I know.
- 你介意我摸你的肚子吗？ - 我不介意你摸我的肚子
- You don't mind me touching your belly?     - I don't mind you touching my belly...
但你的手 好像挡到宝宝的出口了…
...but your hand's kind of blocking the part where the baby's gonna come out.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey!     - Hey.
艾瑞卡 欢迎你的到来 天啊 变这么大了
Hi, Erica. Welcome back to town. Wow, look how big you've gotten.
因为我怀孕了
That's because I'm pregnant.
- 对 我了解 - 好的
- Right. No, I understand. - Oh, okay.
我老是怕别人以为我又肥 胸部又大
I'm just always afraid that people think I'm just fat with big breasts.
不…我了解
No, no, I knew.
- 好 不要盯着她的胸部   - 是她提起的
- Okay, well, stop staring at them.     - She brought them up.
没想到你这么快又回来了
I didn't realize you were coming back so soon.
再过两个星期 我就不能坐飞机了
In a couple weeks I won't be able to travel.
我要她和医生熟悉 并在饭店好好休养
I wanted her to get to know the doctors and get settled into the hotel.
- 她为何不跟你们住在一起？ - 因为我们要搬家了
- Why isn't she staying with you guys?     - Because we're moving in a couple days.
而且 饭店很好玩 有个装满免费零食的小冰箱
Plus, hotels are fun! My room has this little fridge full of free snacks.
艾瑞卡 那不是免费的
Erica, those things aren't free.
那价格 比任何东西都还不合理…
In fact, they have one of the highest markups of any consumer product--
罗斯 她要帮我们生小孩 她要把你吃了都可以
Ross, she's giving us her baby. She can eat you if she wants.
失陪一下
I'll be right back.
天啊 不敢相信你们要搬了
Oh, man, I can't believe you guys are leaving this place.
我知道…
I know. I know.
如果你要你可以搬来这里 租约还在奶奶的名下
You know, you could take it if you want. The lease is still in Nana's name.
不…这里永远是你们的地方 太令人伤感了
No, no. This will always be your place. It would be too sad.
而且 一个月得花多少钱 才喂得饱乔伊？
Plus, how much a month does it cost to feed Joey?
没错 得花两份薪水
Yeah, it takes two incomes.
钱德在吗？我们想去看个电影
Hey, is Chandler here? We talked about catching a movie.
不 他没有时间看电影了
Oh, no, he doesn't have time for that.
你可以去帮他和乔伊 打包客房
You can go help him and Joey pack up the guest room.
打包好呢 还是看性感啦啦队队长喜剧好呢
Hmm. Packing. Sexy cheerleader comedy.
当热心助人的大哥好呢 还是当看学生电影的怪老头好呢
Hmm. Helpful brother. Creepy loner at teen movie.
怪老头…
Creep)'
- 你们在搞什么？ - 试试看 我一点都不痛
- What are you guys doing?     - Try it. I can't feel a thing.
你们在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding?
- 这叫做打包吗？ - 我们正在休息
- This is packing?     - We're taking a break.
从何时…
From?
从跳完弹簧床后
Jumping on the bed.
好了 离瑞秋的送别派对 只剩几小时 还有很多事要做
All right, Rachel's party is in a couple of hours, and there's a lot to do.
罗斯 你有盖勒家的优良血统 由你负责管这些家伙
Ross, you've got Geller blood. You're in charge of these yahoos.
- 没问题   - 很好
- You got it.    - All right.
好了 她说得没错 我们要认真一点
She's right. We gotta get serious.
我们把保丽龙豆豆 倒进他的裤子里 然后踢他
Let's put Styrofoam peanuts down his pants and kick him!
不 兄弟 她说得对 要干活了 我把东西从衣橱拿出来
No, guys, she's right. We should get to work. I'll take stuff out of the closet.
乔伊负责打包 罗斯负责重新包装乔伊包过的
Joey, you pack them, and Ross, you repack whatever Joey packs.
你们有听到铃声吗？
You guys hear a ringing?
- 这是什么东西啊？ - 手铐 还有软毛包围的 不错哦
- What the hell is this?     - Hey, handcuffs. And fur-lined. Nice.
我不晓得你们有这种癖好
I didn't know you guys had it in you.
钱德 你没有妹妹 所以你不晓得…
Chandler, you don't have a sister, so you can't understand...
这让我多心痛
...how much this bums me out.
我不知道摩妮卡有这些东西
I didn't know Monica had these.
或许是她和别的男友用的 可能是理查
Maybe she used them with another boyfriend. Maybe Richard.
为何她和理查用这个 我却没有？我也可以很变态啊
Why would she use them with Richard and not me? I can be kinky.
我曾经穿围巾裸体跳舞给她看
I once did a naked dance for her with scarves.
痛啊 兄弟 痛啊
Bumming hard, guys. Bumming hard.
- 嗨   - 嗨 麦克呢？
- Hey.     - Hey. Where's Mike?
他要公演
Oh, he has a gig.
好像嫁给摇滚巨星一样 你知道吗？
It's kind of like being married to a rock star, you know?
我老公要公演
My husband has a gig.
是吗？在哪里？
Yeah? Where is it?
他替小朋友的 直排轮溜冰派对弹风琴
Oh, he's playing organ for a children's roller-skating party.
劲爆哦
Rock on!
蛮丰盛的哦 都是些什么东西？
Wow, this is quite a spread. What is all this stuff?
我想这是个好机会
Well, I thought this would be a great opportunity to use up all the food...
把不想带到新家的食物都用掉
...that I don't want to move to the new house with me.
好好享受吧 早餐麦片做饼皮的燻牡蛎砂锅
So enjoy. Smoked oyster casserole with a breakfast-cereal crust.
原汁菜豆 甜点是可能坏了的橘子
Kidney beans in their own juices, and for dessert, a questionable orange.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hey.    - Hey.
- 瑞秋在哪里？ - 她先把艾玛放下
- Where's Rach?    - She's putting Emma down.
马上就过来 她现在才体会到要离开了
She'll be over in a second. It just hit her that she's leaving.
情绪有点激动 大家少说点刺激她的话 好吗？
She's kind of emotional, no one say anything to set her off, okay?
好吧
Yeah.
嗨 瑞秋
Hey, Rach. Hey.
她来了
There she is.
大家好
Hi, you guys.
你们忘了我刚才说的吗？
What did I just say?
不…没关系…我没事的
Oh, no, no, no, it's okay. It's okay. I'm gonna be fine.
- 来 我帮你倒杯喝的   - 好的
- Come, I'll make you a drink.    - Okay.
天啊 不敢相信她真的要离开了
Oh, man, I can't believe she's actually leaving.
我该如何向瑞秋道别？
How am I gonna say goodbye to Rachel?
对啊 她曾是我生命中很重要的人
I know, she's been such a big part of my life.
感觉就像 当初《飞越情海》要停播一样
It feels like when Melrose Place got canceled.
我是说…
I mean...
管它的 我就是想念《飞越情海》
<i>Ah, forget it, I miss Melrose Place.</i>
- 我本来有机会可以阻止她的   - 是吗？
- I had a chance to stop her too.     - Yeah?
你能想到玩丢铜板 居然会连续输57次吗？
Who loses 57 coin tosses in a row? You know?
正面她赢 背面我输
Heads, she wins. Tails, I lose.
等一下
Wait a minute.
- 乔伊 想到什么了吗？ - 我忘了拿干洗的衣服了
- Yes, Joe?     - I forgot to pick up my dry cleaning.
你还好吗？
So you doing okay?
不是太好 你们会来看我 对吗？
Well, I've been better. You guys are gonna come visit, right?
当然 等六个月后 限制出境的法令时效过了
Yes. You know, in six months, the statute of limitations runs out...
我就可以出国旅行了
...and I can travel internationally again.
- 我会很想你的   - 我知道
- I'm gonna miss you so much.    - I know.
你知道吗？我有些道别的话 想个别对你们说
You know what? Um, I have some goodbye stuff that I wanted to say...
我本来要等最后再说的 但是…来吧
...to each of you. And I was gonna save it till the end of the night, but come here.
你认为她们在里面做什么？
Hey, what do you think they're doing in there?
如果要我猜 我想可能是…
If I had to guess, I'd say...
瑞秋带着泡泡袋 然后菲比负责打击
...Rachel's putting on the bubble wrap, and Phoebe's doing the punching.
菲比 我不知道该从何说起
Pheebs, I don't even know where to start.
- 好 在你开始说之前   - 额
- Okay, well, before you do...     - Uh-huh.
我知道我们不该送你礼物的
I know we weren't supposed to get you presents...
- 但我还是有东西要给你   - 哦 哦
-...but I do have something for you.     - Oh! Oh!
哦
Oh.
- 这是什么   - 这是棉花棒
- What is it?    - Well, it's a cotton swab...
上面沾有我的口水
...with a bit of my saliva on it...
所以如果你在那里时 他们有能力后制人了
...so that if they perfect the cloning process while you're over there...
你就可以用这里的DNA 制作你自己的菲比
...you can use the DNA to create your own Pheebs.
我会把这个丢掉的
I'm gonna throw this away...
但是非常谢谢你的好意
...but thank you so much for the gesture.
钱德？
Chandler?
我刚在我们的卧室里 在枕头上医现这个东西
Um, I was just in our bedroom, and I found these on my pillow.
是的 我决定要把那留给你 以防理查突然造访
Oh, yes, I decided to leave those out for you in case Richard stops by...
而你也想来玩点奴隶 和小胡子的游戏
...and you want to engage in a little light bondage and mustache play.
你在说什么？这不是我的东西
What are you talking about? These aren't mine.
是吗？
Oh, yeah, right!
别妄想我会再送你围巾裸体舞了
Good luck getting another scarf dance from me.
那是很可怕的惩罚
That would be a terrible punishment.
但是说真的 我从没有看过这东西
But I'm serious, I've never seen these before.
真的吗？那为何会出现在我们的客房呢？
Really? Then what are they doing in our guest room?
瑞秋曾住过那间房
Rachel used to live in that room.
瑞秋戴手铐
Rachel. With handcuffs.
蛮有趣的
Interesting.
乔伊光屁股
Joey's bare ass.
算你赢
Well played.
- 菲比 我爱你   - 我也爱你
- I love you, Phoebe.    - I love you too.
拜托…
Please...
拜托不要
Please don't--
不要变成那种法国泼妇
Don't turn into, you know, a French bitch.
我不会的
I won't.
好 如果我要和大家个别谈 我最好继续下去
All right. Well, if I'm gonna do this, I better keep going.
- 好的   - 好的
- Okay.     - Okay.
- 摩妮卡？ - 什么事？
- Monica?     - Yeah?
- 你可以过来- 下吗？ - 没问题
- Will you come with me?     - Sure.
- 你用的是防水的睫毛膏吗？ - 不是
- Are you wearing waterproof mascara?     - No.
你完蛋了
Oh, you're so screwed.
嗨
H93'-
那是怎么回事？
What was that all about?
她要个别跟每个人道别
She's gonna say goodbye to each of us individually.
你开玩笑的吧？天啊
Are you kidding? Oh, my God.
对啊 我知道 这对你来说更惨 天啊
Yeah, I know. It's gonna be even worse for you. God.
准备好大哭一场吧
Well, just get ready to do some serious crying.
天啊 我无法处理这种状况
Man, I'm not gonna be able to handle this.
现在我知道每学年结束时 我学生的感觉了
Now I know how my students feel at the end of each year.
以及他们为何要故意假装 给我那么差的评比
And why they act out by giving me such bad evaluations.
摩妮卡 好吧
Mon. Okay.
我就直接说我要说的
I better just say what it is I'm gonna say.
过去十年来 如果不是因为你
None of the amazing things that have happened to me in the last 10 years...
我不会过得那么精采
...would have happened if it wasn't for you.
没有一对姐妹 比你跟我更亲密了
No one has been more like a sister to me.
我了解
I know what you mean.
你也像我的姐妹一样
You're like a sister to me too.
我不知道没有你 我该怎么办
I don't know what I'm going to do without you.
你是我交过最棒的朋友
You're the greatest friend I ever had.
你永远在我心中
Seeing you every day.
什么？
What?
你…
You
永远在我心中
See you every day!
太窝心了
That is so sweet!
糟了 她攻陷摩妮卡了
Oh, no, she took down Monica.
我是家族里最爱哭的
And I'm the crier in the family.
天啊 我可能是下一个
Oh, God, I could be next.
或许她不会找我谈 如果我们看起来聊得很起劲的样子
Maybe she won't talk to me if it looks like we're in conversation.
- 好吧   - 所以 你说的关于那件事的事
- Okay.     - That thing you said about the thing...
真的让我联想到另一件事
...it really made me think about that other thing.
- 瑞秋？ - 还好 现在钱德先跟她谈
- Rash?    - Oh, it's okay, Chandler's talking to her.
我真的让你联想到另一件事吗？
I really made you think about that thing, huh?
瑞秋 我想我这里有你的东西哦
Uh, Rach, I think I have something that belongs to you.
我会想念假装你那些 我不懂的冷笑话很好笑的时候
Oh, I'm sure gonna miss pretending to laugh at your weird jokes that I don't get.
不…他们真的是你的 我们在你以前的房间找到的
No, no, they're really yours. We found them in your old room.
这些不是我的东西 或许摩妮卡和…
Well, these aren't mine. Maybe Monica used to use them with--
不要再提理查了
Don't say Richard.
如果他们不是摩妮卡的 也不是你的 那是谁的呢？
Well, if they're not Monica's and they're not yours, then whose are they?
我想你忘了那房间最变态的前房客
I think you're forgetting the kinkiest former resident of that room.
- 菲比   - 来了
- Pheebs!     - Yeah!
我想这些是你的
I think these are yours.
这些不是我的东西 你看他们这么不坚固的样子 拜托
These are not mine. Look how flimsy they are. Come on.
天啊 你试着用这 把男人铐在水管上…
My God, you try to hang a guy from a water pipe with these...
他们一下就折断了
...they'll snap like a piece of licorice.
- 我可以和下和你谈谈吗？ - 当然可以
- Can I talk to you alone for a minute?     - Sure.
你不会真的把男友铐在水管上吧？
You don't really handcuff guys to water pipes do you?
你认为麦克在哪里？
Where do you think Mike really is?
亲爱的
Oh, honey...
让我先说我要说的 因为当我们进入那种情绪时
Let me just saying something because once we get into this...
我可能会因觉得不自在 而说愚蠢的冷笑话
...I'm gonna get all uncomfortable and probably make some stupid joke.
我只想说 我爱你
I just want to say that I-- I love you.
我会想你的
And I'm gonna miss you.
你要离开我好难过
And I'm so sad that you're leaving.
你知道吗？
Oh, you know what?
我们什么都别说了
Let's not say anything else.
我爱你
I love you.
不要抱得那么紧
Not so tight.
- 我很抱歉 再给我一次机会   - 好的
- I'm sorry, give me one more chance.     - Okay.
好
Okay.
- 噢   - 我很抱歉 走吧…
- Oh!     - I'm sorry. Just go. Just go.
我没办法…
I can't. I can't.
- 我想你是下一个 准备好了吗？ - 还没有
- So I guess you're next. You ready?     - I don't think so.
你不可能准备好的 我好几年没像那样哭过了
Oh, you're definitely not. I haven't cried like that in years.
你昨天看六点新闻枕哭过了
You cried yesterday at the 6:00 news.
那老太太被她的修理工人骗了
That old woman was being scammed by her mechanic.
天啊 不敢相信她把我放到最后
God, I can't believe she saved me for last.
他们为何谈那么久？
Why are they taking so long?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是 天啊 出人意外地 乔伊好像应付的很好
But, God, Joey seems to be handling it surprisingly well.
不
No!
好 该我了
Okay, here we go.
- 好吧   - 好
- Well...     - Yeah.
我想我要走了
I think I'm gonna take off.
哈？
Huh?
各位 这是很棒的一晚 非常谢谢你们
Oh, you guys, this was an amazing night. Thank you so much.
我爱你们
I love you.
晚安
Good night.
搞什么鬼？
What?
我没有单独道别吗？
I don't get a goodbye?
幸运的家伙
Lucky bastard.
简直令人不敢相信 她对每个人单独道别 枕我没有
Unbelievable. She says goodbye to everyone but me!
或许她认为你们之间的过去 可能…
Well, maybe she thought that with all of your history, it could be...
- 切尽在不盲中吧   - 还是要说清楚讲明白啊
-...you know, implicit.     - Well, it needs to be "plicit."
好了 大家想想 这一定有个合理的解释
All right, let's think about this. I mean, there's gotta be an explanation.
- 你有做什么让她不高兴的事吗？ - 没有 应该没有
- Did you do anything to make her mad?     - No, I don't think so.
或许她跟我们讲完 就已经精疲力竭了
You know, maybe she was just really spent from our talk.
- 情绪起伏太强烈了   - 对 我也是
- It was pretty intense.     - Yeah, mine too.
- 我的可是上上之选   - 好了
- Mine was a humdinger.     - Okay!
难道我不配吗？不配一些眼泪和拥抱吗？
I mean, don't I deserve anything? I mean, a few tears, a cursory hug?
不是你的拥抱
Not from you!
罗斯 如果你这么生气 你应该去和她谈谈
Ross, if you're this upset, you should go and talk to her.
谈什么呢？你忘了跟我说再见吗？
And say what? You owe me a goodbye?
- 他至少还有点自尊心吧   - 鬼才有
- I mean, he's got more pride than that.     - The hell I do!
- 我居然没有单独道别？ - 什么？
- I don't get a goodbye?     - What?
每个人都有单独道别 为何我没有 要做什么才能得到你的单独道别？
Everyone gets a goodbye but me? What do I gotta do to get a goodbye?
当你的好朋友？和你交拄？
Huh? Be best friends with you? Go out with you?
还是跟你生小孩？
Have a baby with you?
等一下…我想我都做了
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute! I did all those things!
- 罗斯…   - 或许我这样说对你不公平
- Ross--     - Or maybe I'm just not giving you...
毕竟 和五个人说再见是很难得
...enough credit. Uh, I mean, it is difficult to say goodbye to five people.
再见…
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, g--
生理上是不可能做得到的
It's physically impossible!
知道吗？在我们经历过 这么多的事之后
You know what? After all we've been through...
我不敢相信你用这种方式告别
...I can't believe this is how you want to leave things between us.
祝你在巴黎生活愉快
Have a good time in Paris.
- 希望罗斯不会太伤心   - 我相信他不会比我
- I hope Ross isn't too upset.     - I'm sure he's not more bummed out...
- 更伤心   - 就是说啊
-...than I am.     - Tell me about it.
现在知道我们是派对高手了吧
Well, you can't say we don't know how to throw a party.
我该走了
I think I'm gonna head out.
- 你要去哪里？ - 我要回家去睡觉
- Uh, where do you think you're going?     - I thought I was going home to bed...
但是我感到 这里有比较没趣的事给我做
...but I'm sensing there's something less fun for me to do here.
我们要搬家了 还有很多东西没有打包
We're moving in a couple days and we got a lot of packing to do.
- 如果你们能帮忙就太好了   - 乔伊和我去把客房整理完
- It'd be great if you guys could pitch in.     - Joey and I can finish up the guest room.
对 好主意
Yeah, good idea.
不 你和菲比留在这里帮我
Oh, no. You and Phoebe are gonna help me in here.
你就不能冷静一点吗？
You couldn't be cool.
我们从厨房开始
We're gonna start in the kitchen.
盘子放进盘子保护袋中 然后十个一叠装箱
Plates get put into plate protectors and stacked 10 to a box.
银器用橡皮筋捆起来 然后用泡泡袋包裹 知道吗？
The silverware gets bundled in rubber bands and then bubble wrapped. Got it?
- 是的   - 很好 你们要很小心
- Yeah.     - Good. I need you to be careful...
且有效率 请记得 如果我对你们太山了
...and efficient. And remember, if I'm harsh with you...
一定是因为你们做错了
...it is only because you're doing it wrong.
摩妮卡 我知道那手铐是谁的了？
Hey, Mon, I think I figured out whose handcuffs they are.
- 是吗？你怎么知道的？ - 我在整理衣橱时
- You did? How?     - Well, I was cleaning out the closet...
发现了一些
...and I found some pictures of them...
- 使用手铐时的照片   - 天啊 我看看
-...being used.     - Oh, my God, let me see.
那位恶心的老太太是谁？
Who's that dirty old lady?
是摩妮卡的姥姥
Monica's grandmother.
天啊 原来姥姥这么狂野
Oh, my God. Nana liked it rough!
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.   - Hey.
这里 坐下吧 耶
Here, have a seat. Yeah.
- 今天晚上过的怎么样？ - 还不错
- How was your night?     - Oh, it was okay.
我和亲戚去看电影 然后去吃晚饭
I went to a movie with my cousin then out for dinner.
我们去一个地方…
We went to this place that had--
那里有很棒的起司汉堡
Anyway, they had these really amazing cheeseburgers.
- 艾瑞卡 你还好吧？ - 还好 或许我吃太多了
- Erica, are you okay?     - Yeah, you know, maybe I ate too much.
一直有点胃痛 几分钟就痛一次
I keep getting these stomachaches. They come and go every few minutes.
- 天啊   - 别担心 给她点胃药就好了
- Oh, my God.     - Relax, we'll just get her some antacids.
她不是胃痛 是要生了
She doesn't have a stomachache! She's in labor!
- 天啊   - 好 你们要去医院了
- Oh, my God!     - Yeah, you gotta get to the hospital!
钱德 拿外套 艾瑞卡 我们走 乔伊和菲比 继续打包
Chandler, get the coats! Erica, let's go! Phoebe and Joey, keep packing!
天啊 我们要有宝宝了
Oh, my God, we're gonna have a baby.
我们要有宝宝了
We're gonna have a baby!
天啊 我们要有宝宝了
Oh, my God, we're gonna have a baby!
天啊 我得坐下来一下…
Oh, God, I've gotta sit down! I've gotta sit down!
- 亲爱的 没事的   - 你不会有事的 深呼吸
- Honey, it's gonna be okay.     - You can do this. Just breathe.
好…
Okay. Okay.
好了 我好多了
Okay, I feel a little better.
你确定吗？
Oh! Are you sure?
- 对 我确定 亲爱的 我们走吧   - 好
- Yes, I'm sure. Oh, honey, let's go.     - Okay.
- 来吧 我们走了   - 好的 再见 各位
- Come, let's go.     - Bye!
- 我们要有宝宝了   - 祝你们好运
- We're having a baby!     - Good luck!
- 钱德 等- 下…   - 什么事？
- Chandler, wait, wait, wait!     - What?
如果你有空 问她是哪里的起司汉堡
If you get a second, find out where she got that cheeseburger.
你认为我没跟你单独道别 是因为我不在乎你吗？
You think I didn't say goodbye to you because I don't care?
看起来似乎是那样子
That's what it seemed like.
我不敢相信相处了十年 你居然一点也不了解我
I cannot believe that after 10 years you do not know one thing about me!
- 那你为何不说清楚呢？ - 因为太难了 罗斯
- Then why didn't you say something?     - Because it is too damn hard, Ross!
我根本不知道该如何告诉你 我将会有多想你
I can't even begin to explain to you how much I am gonna miss you.
当想到不能天天见到你 我就根本不想走了
When I think about not seeing you every day, it makes me not want to go.
好吗？所以如果你认为 我没单独跟你道别
Okay? So if you think that I didn't say goodbye to you...
是因为你没有其他人重要 你就错了
...because you don't mean as much to me as everybody else, you're wrong.
是因为你太重要了
It's because you mean more to me.
这样 你满意了吧？这是你要的道别
So there, all right? There's your goodbye!
- 瑞秋   - 干嘛？
- Rash!     - What?
- 你一直 你不能…   - 干嘛？
- You keep-- You can't     - What?
- 再多放一点   - 好
- A little more.     - Okay.
- 再多一点…   - 好
- A little more. A little more.     - All right.
再多一点
Little more.
- 好了…来吧   - 好 准备好了吗？
- All right. All right, let's do this.     - All right, ready?
好 奋力一击吧
Yep. Now give me your best shot.
好的 来了哦
All right. Here goes.
一点用都没有
Doesn't work.